One dream,
one wish If you want it,
gotta go over the top!
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Marked maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead to new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
Daddy!
It's not fair!
You can't die!
No one told us.
I thought smiles were just a
kind of man-made Devil Fruit.
Sir Yasui, no!
We weren't fast enough. What now?
Do you think they're going to riot?
You stood right before me.
And I didn't even know.
I failed you.
I should commit sepulchre.
Lord Yasui.
Don't know Yasuhu's gone!
Oh my lord, Yasuhu!
He was taken too soon!
Am I missing something here?
The people from Ebisu Town loved him
so much, why would they be laughing?
This doesn't make sense.
You're a sick bastard, Orji.
You must think this is funny.
Those poor chumps are crazy,
laughing their asses off at
the death of their old daimyo.
You are a bastard, Orochi!
I can scarcely believe it, sir,
Yasui—he was alive all these years?
years He knew about our strategy, and
he knew that the enemy had thwarted it.
Sir Yasui, I see now.
You let them seize you.
Your sacrifice has
given us another chance.
There must be some reason, right?
Huh?
It doesn't matter who it is.
Nobody deserves to be
laughed at when they die.
It's just not right.
This is due to the side
effects of the Smilefruits.
They are here as well.
People who can only laugh
even when they're sad.
You've been gone a while.
Have you seen this?
Do the words Smilefruit ring a bell?
That was my mistake.
I should have told you.
The smiles that the people of
Ebisu wear, they are merely masks.
Masks that they can never
remove till they're dead.
Kaido and Orochi began this
operation a few years ago.
They started importing some
kind of artificial fruit in
exchange for the weapons that
are made in this country.
The smile fruits, when you
eat those wretched things,
you invite the hatred of the sea and
can no longer swim but in return you'll
gain the strength of a wild beast and
their fearsome appearance as well,
all that stuff checks
out with what we know a
while back we destroyed
the factory that made them.
I know master keen did mention that but
their plan had gone on for quite some time!
The damage had been done.
A great number of fruits have
been brought to our country.
Kaido's objective was to
strengthen his ranks by giving
that beastly power to as many
of his underlings as possible.
He wanted the strongest pirate
crew the world had ever seen.
But there's always a catch when
something sounds too good to be true.
The success rate of that artificial
strength enhancer was only 10 percent.
So if 10 people ate one of those fruits,
only one of them would gain an ability.
The other nine would face the consequences
without gaining anything in return.
Of course, they won't
be able to swim anymore,
but the flawed chemical
mixture causes another effect.
Those who fail to inherit the power lose
their ability to express sorrow or anger;
all they can do is laugh.
What so the chemical
mixture she mentioned?
That must be the sad stuff that
Caesar was working on, right?
We knew it was bad news, but this
is pretty sick even for Caesar.
Kaido doesn't care; he'll
sacrifice as many minutes he must.
He just wants that power,
no matter the cost.
Kaido's crew is divided
into three categories;
the power of the fruit
determines your place.
Those who haven't eaten
one and are hoping for a
chance to gain a beast
power are called waiters.
The lucky members who beat the odds and
successfully gained the
power are the gifters.
And the unlucky ones who
ate the fruit and were left
with nothing but endless
laughter are the pleasures.
However,
it seems that Kaido and his twisted
associates found their condition amusing.
And so,
their creation was named
in mockery of the only
expression the pleasures were
capable of making anymore.
A smile.
It seemed odd to me,
calling the fruits that.
But I never thought it would
have such a cruel story.
Those guys really are evil.
The truth is, that's
not even the worst part.
Orochi came up with a
wicked plan when he noticed
most smile fruits were
discarded after a single
bite.
They couldn't produce gifters, but they
still passed on the negative side effects.
So if he wanted to turn people into
pleasures out of cruelty, then he could...
No.
Outside of the Capital, as you know,
is the town of leftovers, where people
were crying and dying of hunger.
Every day, Orochi was disgusted
by the sight of their suffering.
So he mixed in the
failed smile fruits with
the deliveries that came from the capital.
Knowing full well how they would react.
So many apples, and they're still fresh.
This is a treat—let's share everyone!
everyone
Of course, after the first few times, they
knew exactly what they were getting into.
But what choice did they have?
They were starving after all,
and their empty stomachs were
heedless to the consequences.
Thus Ebisertown was born,
a place of sickness and poverty
where everyone wears a smile, no
matter how they suffer.
The tragic place haunted by laughter,
where children can't even mourn?
the death of their parents.
So please,
don't blame them for laughing.
They're the ones hurting, most of all.
Of all the living creatures in the
world, Only a human can laugh, right?
Best of all, it's free.
So why waste a beautiful thing?
You can't die.
Please get up.
it's all his fault
he did this for the sake of cruelty
he robs them of all their joy then
robs them of their ability to breathe
it's too much if this isn't hell
That's what is
What more can he take
Look at how happy they are to see you go,
Yasui A fitting aim You knew this
was my country How arrogant to
think that I would ever let you live
You're lucky you lasted so long,
H-Hog But now You're just a dead rat
And there you have it everybody,
your beloved old daimyo,
the famous Shimotsu
Kiyosui is lying face down,
dead in the dirt like the
miserable vermin he is!
Now laugh your asses off, because
we're all so happy to see him go!
This is the land of Wano,
a bright and joyful place!
Why, you might even mistake it for heaven!
Keep laughing! More! More!
Where'd she go? Don't go!
You shouldn't be in there!
Please, Dock, come back!
Daddy!
Don't leave me!
Please, Daddy!
Please, you have to get up!
Here, Daddy.
I have some medicine that'll help you.
It's that girl!
She came and ate Sabo!
It can't be!
Hey, wait!
You're saying she's
Tonoyasu's daughter? No way!
I'll bring you back. Don't worry.
This medicine here will heal any wound.
This toad oil works just like magic.
My friend who sells it told me so.
You'll be just fine.
I'm sorry, Otoko.
It doesn't perform miracles at all.
I lied to you.
Come back!
What a lucky day?
Seems I found you.
Get out of my way!
Get out of my way! Get
out
of my way!
No!
I should have known.
You are Yasue's daughter as clear as day!
Who else could be so insolent?
You little rat!
You little shit!
It's all your fault!
If you hadn't laughed at
me like a damned fool,
then Komurasaki would
still be alive right now!
I'll kill you!
You're wretched family has been
a pain in my ass for long enough.
Say goodbye.
Now die you little shit!
I'll lose you as well!
Finally, I'll have my revenge!
Oh, my God.
I know those guys.
It's Zorojuro the Magistrate
Killer and Sangoro the Sabo Cook.
Piss off.
Go figure.
Those two are always itching for a fight.
This is going to be a problem.
We can deal with it.
They did the right thing.
Yeah, I'm just glad Otoko is safe.
I've been looking forward
to this execution.
How dare you interrupt it!
When the Shogun wants someone dead?
You step aside!
Even if that brat wasn't Yasue's daughter.
She still committed an unforgivable crime.
Hey, samurai!
Kill all of that filthy rat's allies!
And anyone else who
tries to get in the way!
Yes, sir.
Uh-oh, those guys are
pointing right at us.
I'm thinking that we should run.
Scatter, you bunch of roaches!
Kill them!
Sorry, but I don't have
time for you right now.
I don't have time for you.
Then get out of my way, Browgoro.
Is that supposed to be a joke?
It's Sangoro, stupid, and you
stay out of my way, Masjuro.
Masjuro?
That's right, because your
head looks like a moss ball.
Does not!
I'll chop you to pieces right
along with Odorchi. Oh yeah?
Then I'll kick you to death
right along with Kaido.
You'll do what?
My daddy!
Otaku, thank goodness she's safe.
That man, could he be Zoro Juro's friend?
The swordman is definitely
Zoro, so that's one Straw Hat.
The other is Vince Mokesanji.
Strange wanted poster.
Perhaps all of the Straw Hats
are here in the land of Wano.
Not very subtle.
Defying the Shogun right
in the middle of town.
So what?
Who says we need to be subtle, huh?
Huh?
I'll be as loud as I want.
Also, don't ever call me
a Vinsmoke again. Got it?
I'll make sure they leave
it off your gravestone.
Open fire.
Damn it.
We'll just have to keep at it then.
Next row.
Fire!
Take Odako and run already, damn it!
No, not yet.
He needs to pay.
Those thugs really are
quite stubborn, aren't they?
Here, it's better if you
take her. Wait, what?
Why?
He's looking at me.
Take him out! Hurry up!
I need all that ronin with bullets
before he tries to attack me!
I got this!
Run, Browgoro!
You bastard!
You have no right to
cut through my bullets!
Sucker trap!
I won't be satisfied
till I end you myself!
Hey, Mosshead!
You're not the one calling the shots!
Prepare to fire!
Aw, crap.
No!
We gotta get out of here!
Tonyasu gave his life.
Don't waste that.
Whoa.
One sec, mister.
I'm a firm believer in good old balance.
Good and evil, black and
white, odds and evens.
You really knocked him good,
so let's call it a day.
Yeah.
Let me tell you about our secret, okay?
In this country, we have a name
for our trademark grin. You ready?
We proudly call it the Ebisu Smile!
It's where the place gets its name.
Poverty can't steal our smile.
Yasuie.
Why is he so strong?
Don't tell me the Akasaya
put him up to this!
Come on, useless samurai!
Protect me!
720-caliber Phoenix!
And who is that below that
is boss Kiyoshiro, my lord?
You are far too careless; the execution
site clearly lacks the security you require.
That ronin truly is a menace—I
swear he was trying to murder me!
Hey, Moss Head, what the
hell are you trying to pull?
You're gonna get us all killed!
Something
so big—sneak up on me!
on me
Fire on my signal.
What a busy day.
Even more executions.
So what now?
We can't just sit here
and watch this, right?
It's getting ugly.
We gotta step in and throw down, bros.
No, I object.
We cannot afford to endanger
our plan any further.
Also, we'll become
criminals if we fight them.
Then we won't be able
to act in the capital.
Even so, I can't allow them to
put Lord Yasui's body on display.
Preserving his honor
is the least we can do.
It's not that I disagree, but...
Let's split up for now.
Where should all of us
meet once things cool off?
No, I'm staying here to fight.
It is far too soon.
I cannot speak for the others, but Lord
Odin's allies must remain discreet for now.
He's right.
You two should keep a low profile and head
out while the enemy is
still distracted but I,
our crew started this mess so
we'll take care of it, trust me.
We're used to this sort of thing.
I am grateful.
Let us depart.
We shall leave this in
their capable hands.
Take the Shogun back to the castle.
Don't stop until they're all dead!
Every fool who opposes me must be
dealt with swiftly and violently!
I'm not letting you go!
Kill him, Franky!
And he comes up!
Is he good proof?
But he's just a carpenter
All right, time! Can you dig it?
Who are they?
Where did these people come from?
Huh?
So there you are.
No, that guy stole Lord Yasui's body.
What in the hell is
that guy planning to do?
Don't you worry.
We'll give your buddy a proper burial.
Uh-oh!
Huh?
Who's that?
Oh, hey!
Should've known it was you, Usohachi!
Nice save!
Shoot that man on top of the ladder!
Whoa, wait!
You guys can't snipe the sniper!
That would be too ironic!
Mellow Bellamy, Gigantesco
Narno, and Face!
Thanks a ton, Oroby!
Just how many allies do these people have?
Wait a second, it's that
geisha from the castle.
So she is a magic user.
These are powerful enemies.
Be careful!
Honami, leave them to me!
Out of my way.
Oh, I think not.
Fine, then.
I'll cut through!
I am the Shogun's loyal dog.
Hold up for you, Spector!
Let's wrap this up quick.
Sooner we leave, the better. Agreed.
Special attack, godless combat.
Leel's Lord, he can death for Marlowe!
Now, weapons left!
Tornado temple!
Anyone nearby, we need aid!
A group of rebels are
rioting in Rasetsu Town.
The Shogun said he wants
them dead or alive.
Move in with the intent to kill!
You got this! Go!
Kick their asses!
Hell yeah! Mr.
Straw Hat, those people showing on
the display, are they your crewmates?
Guess I shouldn't cheer,
it's supposed to be a secret.
Well, it's probably okay.
Beat him off!
Yeah, nice! Like that! No!
Stop!
Zorojuro! You can do it!
Well, interesting.
So that moss head dude is
your friend, Straw Hat?
That's the magistrate killer, Zorojuro.
He must be part of your crew.
I love it!
This maniac thinks he can
get away with killing Orochi.
Boo!
Boo! Not now!
I'm busy!
Read the room man.
This is good But sir a new
prisoner just arrived and he's
a famous killer from the flower
capital Should I know him?
Why don't you give me a hint, huh?
Better to see him in person.
I think He'll be coming through there
He doesn't look like much.
The Shogun lost patience with this piece
of trash after failing
an important mission.
Lord Oroji said he's worse than useless,
so you can punish him however you see fit.
Head Kirikamazo, the famous killer.
So that's who you are, huh?
I've heard so much about you.
And one more, sir.
Okay, stop there!
I've got some good news.
We found him while we were
escorting Kamizo here.
And luckily, he wasn't too tough to catch.
Captain Kidd is back where he belongs.
It's Jaggy!
He came to us.
He was yelling something or other,
but I wasn't about to listen.
Instead, I pulled out
my gun and shot him up.
He didn't even try to run away.
So here we are.
Maybe he forgot he had those cuffs
on and still thought he was tough
You dunce, that's almost cute kid
Couldn't have been easy
to break out of here.
So why would he just surrender himself?
Ha ha ha ha!
Hey, stop it!
Come on, dammit! I said stop!
Ha ha!
You always hated your laugh.
This is wrong.
This is messed up.
You never laughed out loud.
You couldn't stand to let
anyone hear it, right?
And if someone out there was stupid
enough to make fun of your laugh,
you'd beat the bastards half to death.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Stop it.
I'm begging you.
You started wearing a mask because you
didn't even like to show your face, right?
That's the man I knew.
What the hell did they do to you?
I've got no clue what happened
after we were separated.
Did Kaido do this?
Horichi, where's everyone else?
Say something!
Come on, turn around.
Why won't you answer me?
KILLER!
What?
That's who he is?
He's gotta be the guy he was with before.
Jaggy must have got caught
when he tried to save him.
He suffered a cruel fate.
They gave him a smile fruit.
Now all of his emotions are locked away,
hidden behind a mask of endless laughter.
Oh, gee, you really are
a heartless monster.
What in the hell did
those bastards do to you?
How dare you?
He's my partner!
Whoever takes this won't pay!
You sons of bitches!
Where's everyone?
Where's my crew?
And that's why you don't screw with me!
Let them go!
Oh, I don't take orders
from you, Pipsqueak.
By the way, I came up with a
little game to live things up.
I kept you all waiting, but
the party's back on track now.
Sumo Inferno, round two!
No mercy this time.
I've added a new rule to
spice things up a bit.
You'll still be fighting
against countless opponents,
and the spikes in your
collars will still kill you.
if you step outside of the ring.
Don't worry, that hasn't changed.
But now,
as long as you're still alive,
the runaway and his happy
little pal will be drowning
in that tank there you
get it if you want them
to come out of the water
you gotta lose your head
you and the old man that's
stupid they're not my
crew they have nothing to
do with me I don't care
cuz you seem pretty angry
so even if you aren't crew
mates they must mean
something to you it must be
because your rivals from
the same generation right
well if you're such a kind and
charitable person you can die
anytime and save them but i'd make
it quick if i were you a little
water goes a long way even if
you're a famous pirate it only takes
five centimeters to drown and no
one can hold their breath forever.
Now let the games begin.
You're a coward!
Why don't you get in here and fight me?
I'll kick your ass and settle this!
I'm sick of your games!
You're not the one calling the shots here.
My house, my rules, kid.
Now sit your ass down.
Mr.
Straw Hat, no!
Listen, punk.
You can't win.
I don't see what makes you so hopeful.
It was never possible for either of
you to make it out of this place alive.
Hope isn't an option, only despair.
This is an execution, you get that?
You're all gonna die.
You don't decide where I die?
That's up to me.
Hey, the hell was that?
Did something happen?
Somebody respond!
Master Queen, we lost contact
with the guards outside!
Finally, we made it.
Now, where's my suit?